[{"id":"1","question":"Which ocean lies on the east coast of the United States?","answer1":"Atlantic","answer2":"Pacific","answer3":"Indian","answer4":"Eastern","correct":"2","type":"geo"},{"id":"2","question":"Which is the world's highest mountain?","answer1":"K2","answer2":"Kilimanjaro","answer3":"Mount Everest","answer4":"Makalu","correct":"4","type":"geo"},{"id":"3","question":"How many Great Lakes are there?","answer1":"5","answer2":"6","answer3":"7","answer4":"3","correct":"2","type":"geo"},{"id":"4","question":"Which is the longest river in the U.S.?","answer1":"Yukon River","answer2":"Colorado River","answer3":"Mississipy River","answer4":"Missoury River","correct":"5","type":"geo"},{"id":"5","question":"The United Kingdom is comprised of how many countries?","answer1":"6","answer2":"5","answer3":"4","answer4":"8","correct":"4","type":"geo"},{"id":"6","question":"Which is the largest city in the world?","answer1":"New York","answer2":"Mexico City","answer3":"Bejing","answer4":"Tokio","correct":"3","type":"geo"},{"id":"7","question":"How many stars on the USA flag are there?","answer1":"50","answer2":"49","answer3":"52","answer4":"51","correct":"2","type":"geo"},{"id":"8","question":"Two triangles with equal sides are considered _____________.","answer1":"Similar","answer2":"Congruent","answer3":"Isosceles","answer4":"Equilateral","correct":"3","type":"math"},{"id":"9","question":"Two angles whose measures have a sum of 180 degrees are called ___________.","answer1":"Supplimentary","answer2":"Acute","answer3":"Right","answer4":"Complimentary","correct":"2","type":"math"},{"id":"10","question":"A triangle has a total of how many degrees?","answer1":"90","answer2":"180","answer3":"360","answer4":"540","correct":"3","type":"math"},{"id":"11","question":"What's the next number in the squence?\r\n2,4,9,11,16...","answer1":"18","answer2":"21","answer3":"23","answer4":"19","correct":"2","type":"math"},{"id":"12","question":"What was the first country to give women the vote in 1893?","answer1":"America","answer2":"Australia","answer3":"New Zealand","answer4":"Iceland","correct":"4","type":"history"},{"id":"13","question":"What year did the Berlin Wall fall?","answer1":"1988","answer2":"1994","answer3":"1991","answer4":"1989","correct":"5","type":"history"},{"id":"14","question":"Who was Garibaldi?","answer1":"A famous Italian painter","answer2":"A famous Italian soldier","answer3":"A famous Italian chef","answer4":"A famous Italian monk","correct":"3","type":"history"},{"id":"15","question":"Who was said to be so beautiful that her face launched a thousand ships?","answer1":"Helen","answer2":"Cleopatra","answer3":"Nefertiti","answer4":"Salome","correct":"2","type":"history"},{"id":"16","question":"Which British monarch popularized the Homgburg which came from the German town of the same name?","answer1":"Louis XIV","answer2":"Edward VII","answer3":"Edward V","answer4":"Winston Churchill","correct":"3","type":"history"},{"id":"17","question":"In which country was the Angel of the North erected in 1998?","answer1":"Italy","answer2":"France","answer3":"England","answer4":"Finland","correct":"4","type":"history"},{"id":"18","question":"Which football player won the most Ballon d'Or","answer1":"Cristiano Ronaldo","answer2":"Ronaldinho","answer3":"Lionel Messi","answer4":"Sasa Ilic","correct":"4","type":"sport"},{"id":"19","question":"Which is the highest-paid athletes of modern times with 1.85 billion dollars?","answer1":"Michael Schumacher","answer2":"David Beckham","answer3":"Tiger Woods","answer4":"Michael Jordan","correct":"5","type":"sport"},{"id":"20","question":"As of january 2020, who is the world no. 1 tennis player?","answer1":"Viktor Troicki","answer2":"Novak Djokovic","answer3":"Rafael Nadal","answer4":"Roger Federer","correct":"4","type":"sport"},{"id":"21","question":"Which country does Milos Raonic represent in tennis?","answer1":"Serbia","answer2":"Montenegro","answer3":"USA","answer4":"Canada","correct":"5","type":"sport"},{"id":"22","question":"How many olympic medals did Usain Bolt win?","answer1":"4","answer2":"7","answer3":"8","answer4":"12","correct":"4","type":"sport"},{"id":"23","question":"How many olympic medals did Michael Phelps win?","answer1":"22","answer2":"28","answer3":"31","answer4":"25","correct":"3","type":"sport"},{"id":"24","question":"In which year did Maradona score a goal with his hand?","answer1":"1986","answer2":"1990","answer3":"1982","answer4":"1978","correct":"2","type":"sport"},{"id":"25","question":"In which city will the 2020 Olypmics be held?","answer1":"Los Angeles","answer2":"Barcelona","answer3":"Belgrade","answer4":"Tokyo","correct":"5","type":"sport"},{"id":"26","question":"In which country were the first Olympic Games held?","answer1":"Greece","answer2":"Serbia","answer3":"Angola","answer4":"England","correct":"2","type":"sport"},{"id":"27","question":"How many players has a hockey team got on the ice?","answer1":"5","answer2":"6","answer3":"4","answer4":"8","correct":"3","type":"sport"},{"id":"28","question":"What's the well known name for a painting on a freshly plastered wall?","answer1":"Watercolor","answer2":"Aquarelle","answer3":"Fresco","answer4":"Pastel","correct":"3","type":"art"},{"id":"29","question":"Which artist painted the Poppy Field in 1873?","answer1":"Paul Cezanne ","answer2":"Jan Vermeer ","answer3":"Raphael ","answer4":"Claude Monet","correct":"5","type":"art"},{"id":"30","question":"What is the meaning of the art term impasto?","answer1":"Oily paint","answer2":"Thickly applied paint","answer3":"Watery paint","answer4":"Transparent paint","correct":"3","type":"art"},{"id":"31","question":"What are the three drooping objects in The Persistence of Memory by Salvador Dal\u00ed?","answer1":"Shoes","answer2":"Telephones","answer3":"Clocks","answer4":"Ants","correct":"4","type":"art"},{"id":"32","question":"Which arts' movement was founded by Pablo Picasso and Georges Braque?","answer1":"Cubism","answer2":"Surrealism","answer3":"Impressionism","answer4":"Art Nouveau","correct":"2","type":"art"},{"id":"33","question":"Complete the Van Gogh painting title: 'Starry Night Over the ...'?","answer1":"Sky","answer2":"Rhone","answer3":"Month","answer4":"Winter","correct":"3","type":"art"},{"id":"34","question":"When did the Chetnobyl nuclear catastrophe occur?","answer1":"1963","answer2":"1986","answer3":"1982","answer4":"1974","correct":"3","type":"history"},{"id":"35","question":"What river runs through Baghdad?","answer1":"Karun","answer2":"Jordan","answer3":"Euphrates","answer4":"Tigris","correct":"5","type":"geo"},{"id":"36","question":"What percentage of the River Nile is located in Egypt?","answer1":"83%","answer2":"22%","answer3":"100%","answer4":"5%","correct":"3","type":"geo"},{"id":"37","question":"What is the largest country on the Arabian Peninsula?","answer1":"Jordan","answer2":"Yemen","answer3":"Saudi Arabia","answer4":"United Arab Emirates","correct":"4","type":"geo"},{"id":"38","question":"What city is the capital of Australia?","answer1":"Meblbourne","answer2":"Sydney","answer3":"Perth","answer4":"Canberra","correct":"5","type":"geo"},{"id":"39","question":"Riyadh is the capital of what Middle-Eastern country?","answer1":"Saudi Arabia","answer2":"Syria","answer3":"Yemen","answer4":"Iraq","correct":"2","type":"geo"},{"id":"40","question":"Which two countries are currently fighting in the so called 'Middle East Cold War'?","answer1":"Iran and Syria","answer2":"Iran and Saudi Arabia","answer3":"Israel and Palestine","answer4":"Lebanon and Jordan","correct":"3","type":"geo"},{"id":"41","question":"How tall is Avala mountain?","answer1":"634","answer2":"576","answer3":"480","answer4":"511","correct":"5","type":"geo"},{"id":"42","question":"Who is credited as the designer of the many statues which decorated the Parthenon?","answer1":"Phidias","answer2":"Praxiteles","answer3":"Scopas","answer4":"Hesiod","correct":"2","type":"art"},{"id":"43","question":"Which artist started painting at 27 and died at 37?","answer1":"Pablo Picasso","answer2":"Van Gogh","answer3":"Da Vinci","answer4":"Rembrant","correct":"3","type":"art"},{"id":"44","question":"Which one of the following pieces belongs to Marina Abramovic?","answer1":"The Artist Is Present","answer2":"The Scream","answer3":"The Artist is Still","answer4":"The Torture Room","correct":"2","type":"art"},{"id":"45","question":"How many paintings did Vincent Van Gogh sell during his lifetime?","answer1":"842","answer2":"27","answer3":"193","answer4":"1","correct":"5","type":"art"},{"id":"46","question":"Which of the following paintings were most expensively sold? ","answer1":"Salvator Mundi","answer2":"Interchange","answer3":"Vase with Fifteen Sunflowers","answer4":"The Anatomy Lesson of Dr. Nicolaes Tulp","correct":"2","type":"art"},{"id":"47","question":"How many versions of The Scream did Edvard Munch create?","answer1":"1","answer2":"3","answer3":"5","answer4":"7","correct":"4","type":"art"}]